These classes, they take a, if we want to be able to instantiate them and pass in arguments
to them, like we did within, we need to make a special type of method.
That's called the initializer method.
And it starts with these double underscores, or dunder in it.
What do these double underscores tend to mean?
Yeah, it's special.
So you shouldn't be calling this initializer method directly.
Kind of happens under the hood.
I'm going to print out does wrong.
And I'm going to access runs, like runs is a, is a class variable, right?
So if I run this code, well, the syntax highlighter here is giving you a little bit of a hint,
but I forgot something.
Let's say I didn't have this at all.
I'm just going to print out your car.
Sometimes highlighters still giving us a hint there.
Why is that?
It's because I'm missing something.
And so.
Right.
So self is a required argument to in it.
It's kind of a hidden one.
You don't have to explicitly pass it in.
I'm going to import something so that I can pull in the newest version of my car classes,
and modify it.
So if you're following along with me in this by using a file,
you'll have to do this as well.
So you would have to import, import lib, and then say import lib dot reload,
and the name of your package.
In this case, it's cars.
If I can just type today.
Oh, the reload must be a module.
Okay, so to do this kind of live reload in the Ripple,
not something that we usually do.
Usually we're either working just in the Ripple or just with files.
I would need to import cars as a module.
And then I can say import lib dot reload and give the package name of cars.
And that'll just reload it for my session.
Make sense?
So now if I want to make a new car, I just have to say cars dot car.
And to verify that the type of that is a class type.
Okay.
So if I try to make a new car now.
I'm not going to be able to access any sort of instance variables on it.
And we'll see here that the linter is giving me a hint on that.
So in order to do that, I'm going to have to pass it in self.
And let's change things around a little bit.
I'm just going to close this.
I don't want to specify a new name every time I start my car.
It doesn't make sense, right?
When I make my new car instance, I should be able to say what the type of it is,
or I'm sorry, what the model of my car is once,
not every time I start it to just know.
So I'm going to move this name variable.
I'm going to move that into the init.
What do I need to do to save it to the instance?
Self.name equals name.
Okay.
Now I can take a cell.
Am I passing a name into the start method here?
I'm not.
I still have to pass it in self to signify that this is an instance method.
Now I can still access self.name.
But I don't have access to it in this particular method.
And it's all via the magic of self.
So let me reload this.
And now I can say my Subaru equals cars.car.
And I'm going to give it a name of Subaru.
And cool, new car.
Now I can say my Subaru dot runs starts.
I don't know why I got runs into my head.
My Subaru dot starts.
Start.
Thank you guys.
My Subaru dot start.
And start knows that the name of my car is Subaru.
Why are that instance variable?
Okay.
It's kind of the basics of classes here.
Self refers to an instance.
So the method start?
Yes.
The way it reads self.name is when this program initializes.
That's where self.name.
I'm just wondering how it reads ten.
So let's say I had a new car.
My Mustang equals cars dot car.
What do we know about positional arguments?
They're required, right?
And they have to be passed in an order.
So now if I try to make a new car.
And I don't pass in that name argument.
What's going to happen?
I'm going to get a type error.
It's going to tell me that in it is missing one required positional argument of name.
So I know that if I have an instance of a car because I'm asking for it.
In the beginning constructor.
And I'm setting self.name is name.
I know that it's guaranteed to be there as a variable.
To show you one more time.
It looks like I didn't correctly reload my module.
So let me show you if I make an init.
And that does not take self.
And let me correctly reload this time.
If I say cars dot car.
If I try to make a new instance now.
I'm going to get a type error.
It says init takes zero positional arguments.
But one was given.
What positional argument was given?
We didn't pass any in.
Self.
Exactly right.
That that binding happens under the hood.
Right.
So when you make a new instance of a class.
Python will always pass in.
Self has the first argument.
Okay.
And so let me make sure to pass a not name argument again.